Finding Aid for WUOM Records, 1914-1982
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Paper Records 1920s-1970s
  - Manager's Files
    - E.G. Burrows, 1957-1972
      - National Educational Radio (NER) (cont.)
        - Public Broadcasting Act of 1967
          - Burrows Public Statements (Box 4)
          - Burrows Reference Files (Box 4)
          - Correspondence (Box 4)
          - Memoranda to Executive Committee re: S. 1160 (Box 4)
          - NER Memoranda and Press Releases (Box 4)
          - Testimonies in Support of H.R. 6736 (Box 4)
          - Testimonies in Support of S. 1160, 2 folders (Box 4)
        - Reorganizational Study 1967 (Box 4)
        - Bound Volume
          - Memos to Managers 1964-1969 (Box 4)
      - WUOM
        - Awards (American Federation for the Blind; Armstrong Memorial Research Foundation) (Box 4)
        - Correspondence 1960s (Box 4)
        - FCC Inquiry re: Revision of FM Broadcasting Rules (correspondence and reference materials) 1966-1967 (Box 4)
        - NAEB Educational Communications Systems (ECS) Project 1964-1966
          - Correspondence (Box 4)
          - Midwest Feasibility Model (Box 4)
          - Reports and Memoranda (Box 4)
        - One Nation Indivisible 1956-1958
          - Correspondence (Box 4)
          - Grant Request and Administrative Records (Box 4)
          - Press Releases and Publicity (Box 4)
        - Original Productions
          - The American Town: A Self-Portrait (Box 4)
          - Michigan Names (Box 4)
          - News in Twentieth Century America (Box 4)
          - Orestes (Box 4)
        - Press Releases 1957-1967 (scattered dates) (Box 4)
        - Program Summaries (monthly reports) 1968-1970, 3 folders (Box 4)
        - Response to NER Survey 1966 (Box 4)
        - Survey of Radio Stations using WUOM Distributed Programming 1965 (Box 4)
        - Tenth Anniversary July 5, 1958 (Box 4)
      - WVGR
        - Clippings 1961-1962 (Box 4)
        - Correspondence 1960-1962 (Box 4)
        - Dedication Program December 9, 1961 (Box 4)
        - Programming Proposals (Box 4)
        - Publicity and Promotion 1961-1962 (Box 4)
    - Neal Bedford (1972-1984)
      - Publicity (Box 4)
  - Radio Classroom
    Radio Classroom series (.5 linear ft.). For twenty years (1951-1971) WUOM was a leader in offering radio instruction to schools in the State of Michigan. Though the size and depth of this series in no way reflect the influence enjoyed by the programs in the Radio Classroom series, it is significant that the bulk of the records document the development of the first and most popular of the programs, "Festival of Song." Taught by faculty in the School of Music, "Festival" was offered from October through April to schools desiring classroom music instruction. Included in the records are scripts and performance notes, and programs, correspondence, itineraries, and related materials concerning the program's annual spring tour.
    - "Festival of Song"
      - Correspondence 1960-1971 (scattered dates) (Box 5)
      - Correspondence (Department of Defense Overseas Dependents Schools) 1967-1970 (Box 5)
      - Grant Application (Tahquamenon [Michigan] Area School District) (Box 5)
      - Lesson Plans and Performance Notes (Box 5)
      - Miscellaneous (journal notes, student artwork, resource lists, etc.) (Box 5)
      - Scripts 1967/68-1970/71, 7 folders (Box 5)
      - Spring Tour 1951-1971, 7 folders (Box 5)
      - Survey of Participating Schools, ca. 1971 (Box 5)
    - "The Great Lakes"
      - Teacher's Guides (Box 5)
    - Publicity 1951-1953, undated (Box 5)
    - School Radio Programs [teacher's guides] (bound) 1953/54-1954/55, 1 volumes
      - "Festival of Song" (Box 5)
      - "Meeting the Situation" [non-WUOM] (Box 5)
      - "Learning Outdoors" (Box 5)
      - "Tales of the Talking Stone" (Box 5)
      - "Sky Trails" (Box 5)
      - "Milestones of Freedom" (Box 5)
      - Piano Accompaniment for "Festival of Song" (Box 5)
      - "A Name to Remember" (Box 5)
      - "Messages and Men" (Box 5)
      - "Red Man in Michigan" (Box 5)
      - "Our Schools" (Box 5)
      - "Visitons Mimi" [French language course] (Box 5)
      - "Adventures in Research" (Box 5)
      - "Story Time" (Box 5)
      - "Vacation Land" (Box 5)
  - Radio Scripts [bound]
    Radio Scripts series (9 linear ft.). Both bound and unbound, these consist of original scripts produced and broadcast by WUOM staff and transcripts of talks given by University of Michigan faculty. The "pre-WUOM" scripts date from the early 1930s to 1946 and chiefly consist of faculty radio talks. The "WUOM" scripts primarily correspond to the original dramatic/documentary program series produced by WUOM in the late 1940s to mid-1950s. The bulk of the scripts are in bound volumes.
    - pre-WUOM
      - Children's Radio Programs [dramatizations of children's literature], ca. 1940s (Box 6)
      - Mimeographed Radio Talks of 1933-1934 [selection based on listener response] (Box 6)
      - Radio Art Programs ca. 1932-1941 (Box 6)
      - "An Art Pilgrimage to Famous Museums," programs #2-9, 11-19 (Box 6)
      - "American History as Told by American Artists," programs #1-19 (Box 6)
      - "Art Appreciation Series," programs #1-5 (Box 6)
      - "Union Pacific," 1938 (Box 6)
        (Paramount Pictures script signed by C.B. DeMille, Barbara Stanwyck, Joel McCrea, Akim Tamiroff, Robert Preston, and Lynne Overman)
      - University of Michigan Broadcast Service (Box 6)
        (Publicity, 1933-1936 Forestry, Economic Stability and Unemployment Relief; Child's Own Bookshelf; Problems and Methods of Character Education; Economic Series of 1931-32; Art Appreciation Series, 1932-33)
      - University of Michigan Original Radio Plays 1946 (Box 6)
      - University of Michigan Radio Medical Talks, Vol. 1 circa 1932-1941 (Box 6)
      - University of Michigan Radio Medical Talks 1942-1943 (Box 7)
      - University of Michigan Radio Plays: Adaptations [excerpts from classic fiction] undated (Box 7)
      - University of Michigan Radio Programs: Dramatized Legal Information
        - "From Legal History," 1941 (Box 7)
        - "Out of Court," undated (Box 7)
      - University of Michigan Radio Programs [series]
        - "Game of the Week," 1939-1940 (Box 7)
        - "Know Your [Michigan] Cities," 1940-1941 (Box 7)
        - "Tell Me, Professor," 1943-1944 (Box 7)
        - "It's the Bunk" [superstitions] 1940 (Box 7)
        - "World Masterpieces: Nineteen Quiz Programs on Music and Literature," 1946-1947 (Box 7)
      - University of Michigan Radio Talks, 23 volumes
        - Anthropology, Archaeology, Botany, Landscape Design, Geology, Zoology, ca. 1930-1942 (Box 7)
      - Architecture, Economics, Languages, Mathematics, Sociology, ca. 1931-1939 (Box 8)
      - Astronomy; Botany; Chemistry; Dentistry; Nursing; Pharmacy, ca. 1930s-1940s (Box 8)
      - Clements Library; English; Hobby Series; Living for Moderns; Medical Series, 1947-48; Social Service; Sponsored Research; English Engineering; Miscellaneous (Box 8)
      - English; English Engineering (Box 8)
      - Engineering Series, ca. 1931-1942 (Box 8)
      - Forestry and Conservation, ca. 1930-1941 (Box 8)
      - Guidance, Delinquency, Children's Problems, ca. 1935-1944 (Box 9)
      - Historical Dramas, ca. 1938-1942 "Little Known Facts in American History;" "It Happened Before" (World War II Series) (Box 9)
      - Home Planning Series, Fall 1935 Medical Series, 1945-1946 (Box 9)
      - Literature Series; Forensic Series (Box 9)
      - Marital Relations Series; Health Series; Pharmacy Series (Box 9)
      - Medical Series 1946-1947 (Box 9)
      - Michigan, My Michigan 1934-1936, 2 volumes (Box 9)
      - Parent Education Programs: Mental Hygiene of Adolescence; Adult Education; Vocational Guidance; Speech; Language 1934-1935 (Box 9)
      - Parent Education Programs: Michigan, My Michigan; Geography and Travel; Eras in English Literature; Critical Moments in the Lives of Nations; Home Planning, Building and Maintenance; Current Events and University Research 1935-1936 (Box 9)
      - Pharmacy, Physics, History, Business Administration, Economics, and Finance 1946-1947 (Box 10)
      - Speech, Dramatics (Box 10)
      - Speech, Journalism, Political Science, ca. 1934-1938 (Box 10)
      - Vocational Guidance, 2 volumes (Box 10)
      - Youth Delinquency; Guidance; Health; Michigan, My Michigan (Box 10)
      - Writers' War Board: Radio Plays 1942-1946 (Box 10)
    - WUOM
      - "American Industry;" "Sky Trails;" "Soo Adventure," 1950-1954 (Box 11)
      - "A Gallery of Women;" "Julius Caesar;" "Learning Outdoors," 1951-1954 (Box 11)
      - "The Golden Queen," 1951-1952 (Box 11)
      - "Michigan Names;" "The Tunnelers," 1959-1960 (Box 11)
      - "A Name to Remember (national);" "The Musicmakers," 1951-1952 (Box 11)
      - "One Nation Indivisible," 1957-1958 (Box 11)
      - "Panorama," 1956/57-1960/61, 3 volumes (Box 12)
      - Radio Guild Dramas 1952-1957 (Box 12)
      - Radio Medical Series 1948-1956, 2 volumes (Box 12)
      - "Rx for Health," 1956-1963 Miscellaneous Programs, 3 volumes (Box 13)
      - "Tales of the Valiant," 1955 (Box 13)
      - "They Fought Alone," 1953 (Box 13)
      - "Treasures Off the Shelf," 1949 (Box 13)
  - Radio Scripts [unbound]
    - pre-WUOM
      - "American Revolution" [drama], ca. 1938 (Box 14)
      - "Heroes of Medicine" [drama] February-April 1942 (Box 14)
      - "Hobby Series," Undated (Box 14)
      - "Hymns of All Churches," September-October 1938 (Box 14)
      - Miscellaneous 1939, 1946
        - Interview with Edward W. Blakeman March 9, 1939 (Box 14)
        - University of Michigan Anniversary Program March 18, 1939 (Box 14)
        - [Campus news summary] April 1946 (Box 14)
        - Special Laboratory Program (University of Michigan and CBS, co-producers): "Ex-Soldier;" August 16, 1944 (Box 14)
      - Talks by University of Michigan Faculty 1930s-1940s, Undated (Box 14)
      - "Vocational Guidance Series," 1940-1941 (Box 14)
      - "The World This Week" (Preston Slosson) April 27, 1941 (Box 14)
      - "A Dickens of a Christmas," December 24, 1970 (Box 14)
      - "Messages and Men," programs #1-7, 9-13 (Box 14)
      - Michigan Union Dedication Program October 1954 ["Sesquicentennial"] (Box 14)
      - "Money, Machines, and Music," programs #1-10, 13 1964 (Box 14)
      - "A Name to Remember" [Michigan], programs #1-28, 3 folders (Box 14)
      - "The News from Dallas," November 1964 (Box 14)
      - "Radio Guild," programs #1, 3-7, 12 1951-1952 (Box 14)
      - "To Make Men Free," programs #1-[3] (Box 14)
      - "Toward Peace," programs #1-15 (Box 14)
      - "[Tribute to] Waldo Abbot," November 4, 1964 (Box 14)
    - WUOM: Program Series
      - "Union Voices," programs #1-26 (Box 14)
  - Visual Material
    Visual Material (1.25 linear ft. and 1 outsize volume). Although including photographs--mostly pertaining to "Festival of Song" tours, this series consists predominantly of scrapbooks which, through newspaper clippings and other promotional material, document WUOM's broadcast activity from the 1940s through the 1960s.
    Sound Reels: Accompanying Materials (.25 linear ft.). Press releases, announcers' cue sheets, news clippings and other materials which were used by WUOM staff in broadcast production, and which provide helpful background and/or summary information regarding the recordings. Originally stored with individual sound reels, they have been removed and filed separately for preservation reasons.
    - Photographs
      - Awards and Programs
        - "Festival of Song", 6 envelopes
          - Adult Performers (Box 14)
          - Candid Portraits and Audiences (Box 14)
          - Children Performers (Box 14)
          - 1953 [Spring] Festival (Box 14)
          - 1960 [Spring] Festival (Box 14)
          - Negatives (Box 14)
      - WVGR Dedication (Box 14)
    - Scrapbooks
      - "News in 20th Century America", 3 folders (Box 14)
      - "They Fought Alone", 1 volumes (Box 15)
      - "Treasures Off the Shelf", 1 volumes (Box 15)
      - Broadcasting Service of the University of Michigan 1925-1950, 1 volumes (Box 15)
      - Clippings 1952, 1 folders (Box 15)
        (loose, from WUOM Clipping Scrapbook, 1948-1951
      - [WUOM] 1952-1969, 2 folders (Box 15)
      - [WUOM Clipping Scrapbook] 1948-1951 (Box 15)
      - Scrapbook, "The Michigan Radio Classroom," 1953 (Volume 1)
        (BImu/C471)
  - Sound Reels: Accompanying Materials
    - Sound Reels (7-inch)
      - Cue sheets, press releases, and clippings 1960s (Box 16)
        (for reels R59A-R149A)
    - Sound Reels (10.5"), 2 folders
      - Cue sheets, press releases, and clippings 1960s-1970s (Box 16)
        (for reels R159B-R284B)
- Audio Material 1930s-1970s
  Ranging in date from the 1930s into the 1980s, the sound recordings have been arranged first by format into two groups, sound reels and sound discs; the sound reels have been further arranged by size. Thus, there are three separate series of sound recordings: sound reels (7-inch); sound reels (10 1/2-inch); and sound discs. The recordings within each series have been arranged by provenance and content into the following subseries:
  WUOM: Anniversaries and Dedication Programs
  WUOM: Original Productions, 1949-1967
  WUOM: Program Series, 1948-1990
  U-M Ceremonies and Convocations, 1961-1969
  U-M Conferences and Lectures, 1961-1969
  U-M History, 1958, 1961
  U-M Sesquicentennial Celebration, 1967
  State and Local History and Events, 1950, 1960, undated
  Each recording has been assigned an inventory number which is listed in brackets following the item description in the boxlist. This number designates whether the recording is a reel (prefix "R") or a disc (prefix "D"), the recording's numeric sequence, and, for sound reels, the size ("A" for 7", "B" for 10.5"). Unless otherwise noted, reel playback speed is 7.5 inches per second (ips).
  - Audition Copies
    Audition Copies (.75 linear ft.). Select sound reels have been duplicated as cassettes for the use of researchers. Audition copies include such heavily used recordings as John F. Kennedy's speeches in Ann Arbor on October 13-14, 1960, and Lyndon B. Johnson's 1964 "Great Society" commencement address. (Numbers in brackets indicate corresponding sound reel[s])
    - Fonda, Jane December 1, 1970, [R234B] (Box 16)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., Commencement May 22, 1964, [R182B] (Box 16)
    - Kennedy, John F., at Michigan Union October 13-14, 1960, 2 audiocassettes; [R147A-R148A] (Box 16)
    - Kennedy, John F., leaving Ann Arbor October 14, 1960, [R149A] (Box 16)
    - McNamara, Robert S., Commencement June 12, 1962, [R181B] (Box 16)
    - Murrow, Edward R., Commencement June 17, 1961, [R96A-R97A] (Box 16)
    - Roethke: A Tribute, [R15A-R16A] (Box 16)
    - Warfield, William, Music School August 12, 1985 (Box 16)
    - Taylor, Billy, Music Schol August 12, 1985 (Box 16)
    - Poetry reading January 24, 1986 (Box 16)
      (Seamus Heaney, Galway Kinnell, Donald Hall, Wendell Berry)
  - Sound Reels (7-inch)
    - WUOM: Anniversary and Dedication Programs
      WUOM: Anniversaries and Dedication Programs consist of recordings of programs produced to commemorate special events in the history of radio station WUOM.
      - Dedication Program: Silver Anniversary of University of Michigan Broadcasting Service and Dedication of WUOM and New Studios, broadcast January 14, 1950, [R1A] (Box 17)
        (dub November 16, 1964)
    - WUOM: Original Productions
      The subseries WUOM: Original Productions is comprised of recordings of dramatic and/or documentary programs or program series written, performed, and produced by WUOM staff, often in conjunction with university faculty and students. Except in a very few instances, only a representative sampling of recordings were retained for each series. Items of uncertain date or undated are listed first.
      - Archives Anthology, recorded 1950s, 3 3/4 ips; [R2A]
        - Interview: E.G. Burrows with Eleanor Steber, broadcast Guest of Honor (Box 17)
        - Interview with Willie Heston, broadcast Guest of Honor undated (Box 17)
        - Interview with Ogden Nash (Box 17)
        - Interview: [T. Hawley Tapping] with Louis Elbel (re: "Victors") (Box 17)
        - Dramatization: J. Fred Lawton portrays Fielding H. Yost (Box 17)
      - Dialogue: J. Fred Lawton and Earl V. Moore discuss writing of "Varsity"; Michigan Marching Band playing "Varsity" (Box 17)
      - Charles Ives Dared [reading with musical accompaniment] / E.G. Burrows; Leonard Bernstein; New York Philharmonic Orchestra, recorded [1950s ?] Biographical Tribute to American Composer, Charles Ives (15 ips), [R3A] (Box 17)
      - Interview with Harriet Arnow/Ralph Johnson, interviewer, recorded March 28, 1969, 2 reels; [R4A-R5A] (Box 17)
        (Reminiscences of Arnow's early life in Appalachia)
      - May Festival Interview: Eugene Ormandy with E.G. Burrows, recorded April 22, 1968, [R6A] (Box 17)
      - Michigan Week Special Broadcasts 1959-1966, 7 reels (Box 17)
      - 1959
        - Interview with F. Clever Bald, recorded April 30, 1959 broadcast May 1959, [R7A] (Box 17)
      - 1960
        - [Full Employment in Michigan] / report by William Haber, recorded April 29, 1960 broadcast May 19, 1960, [R8A] (Box 17)
        - Tribute to Chase Osborn, recorded April 30, 1960 broadcast May 1960 (15 ips), [R9A] (Box 17)
        - [Michigan] Folk Songs, recorded May 2, 1960 broadcast May 1960 (15 ips), [R10A] (Box 17)
      - 1961
        - Red Man in Michigan #1: The Tribes, recorded May 10, 1961 (Box 17)
        - Michigan Geology: Interview with Don [Eshman?] and Jack [Dorr?], recorded May 10, 1961, [R11A] (Box 17)
      - 1962
        - Interview with James Wilson, recorded 1962 (Box 17)
        - Interview with [____] Hausel, recorded 1962 (Box 17)
        - Interview with Robert Warner re: Stevens T. Mason Papers, recorded 1962, [R12A] (Box 17)
      - 1964
        - [Michigan's Natural Resources and Conservation]: interview with Archibald B. Cowan, recorded May 8, 1964, [R13A] (Box 17)
        - [Michigan's Economy]: interview with Roblee Martin, recorded May 11, 1964, [R14A] (Box 17)
      - 1965
        - [Theodore] Roethke: A Tribute / E.G. Burrows, host; Allan Seeger; Donald Hall; A.J.M. Smith; Nelson Bentley; recording of Theodore Roethke--recorded May 12, 1965 broadcast May 23, 1965, 2 reels; [R15A-R16A] (Box 17)
          (Audition copy available in Box 16.)
      - 1966
        - Michigan Folk Songs, broadcast May 18, 1966 (Box 17)
        - Issues in Conservation 1966 / Douglas Fulton, broadcast May 17, 1966, [R17A] (Box 17)
        - University of Michigan Sesquicentennial--broadcast May 19, 1966, [R18A] (Box 17)
        - Cooperative Education Ventures, broadcast May 17, 1966 (Box 17)
        - Interview with Chief Herbert Welsh, broadcast May 21, 1966, [R19A] (Box 17)
      - "Tales of the Valiant" broadcast October-December 1955, 1 reel of [13] retained
        (award-winning drama-documentary, scripts available in WUOM paper record series)
        - Program #13: Jose Rizal [Philippines], broadcast December 29, 1955, [R20A] (Box 17)
      - "To the Cornflower and the Maize," 1965-1966, 20 reels
        ([Oral history-documentary produced for University of Michigan Sesquicentennial] recorded 1965-1966, broadcast weekly beginning January 1967. Traces the historical development of the university from founding to the 1950s)
        - Program #1: "The Classical Greek on the Old Frontier" / F. Clever Bald; Robert Warner; Howard Peckham; Russell Bidlack; Philip Bursley, broadcast January 8, 1967, [R21A] (Box 17)
        - Program #2: "The Athens of the West" / Russell Bidlack; Robert Warner; F. Clever Bald, broadcast January 15, 1967, [R22A] (Box 17)
        - Program #3: "Preachers as Teachers" / Russell Bidlack; Robert Warner; F. Clever Bald, broadcast January 29, 1967, [R23A] (Box 17)
        - Program #4: "Shaping a University," pt. 1 Robert Warner; E. Blythe Stason; Russell Bidlack; F. Clever Bald; Howard Peckham; Philip Bursley; Harrison Randall, broadcast February 5, 1967, [R24A] (Box 17)
        - Program #5: "Shaping a University," pt. 2 Howard Peckham; Hazel Losh; Henry Frieze Vaughn; Wells Bennett; Russell Bidlack, broadcast February 12, 1967, [R25A] (Box 17)
        - Program #6: "Michigan at Fifty Years" / Russell Bidlack; Howard Peckham; A.D. Moore; Charles Sink; George Carrothers, broadcast February 19, 1967, [R26A] (Box 17)
        - Program #7: "In Pursuit of a President" / Harrison Randall; Philip Bursley; Henry Carter Adams II; Charles Kennedy; Howard Peckham, broadcast February 26, 1967, [R27A] (Box 17)
        - Program #8: "Literature, Science and Arts" / Hazel Losh; William Trow; Howard Peckham; Philip Bursley; I. Leo Sharfman; William Paton, broadcast March 5, 1967, [R28A] (Box 17)
        - Program #9: "The Glorified Blacksmith Shop" / Henry Carter Adams II; Wells Bennett; Howard Peckham; A.D. Moore; Ruel Churchill; Samuel Dana; Roscoe Bonisteel, broadcast March 12, 1967, [R29A] (Box 17)
        - Program #10: "Medicine at Michigan" / Helen Hebelar; Arthur Furstenberg; Henry Frieze Vaughn; Charles Kennedy, broadcast March 19, 1967, [R30A] (Box 17)
        - Program #11: "Michigan at 75 Years" / Howard Peckham; A.D. Moore; Ralph Sawyer; Harrison Randall; Hazel Losh; Henry Carter Adams II; Charles Sink--broadcast April 2, 1967, [R31A] (Box 17)
        - Program #12: "Golden Age of Student Life" / Howard Peckham; A.D. Moore; Philip Bursley; Harrison Randall; Henry Carter Adams II; Charles Kennedy--broadcast April 9, 1967, [R32A] (Box 17)
        - Program #15: "Michigan at 100 Years" / Margaret Tracy; I. Leo Sharfman; Henry Carter Adams II; Roscoe Bonnisteel; Helen Hebelar; William Paton; Charles Sink, broadcast April 30, 1967, [R33A] (Box 17)
        - Program #16: "A Time for Building" / Preston Slosson; Charles Sink; A.D. Moore; Philip Bursley; Wells Bennett; Margaret Tracy; Roscoe Bonnisteel; William Trow; George Carrothers; Helen Hebelar, broadcast May 7, 1967, [R34A] (Box 17)
        - Program #17: "The Yankee Rebel" pt. 1 / Clarence Cook Little; Margaret Tracy; George Carrothers; Henry Carter Adams II, broadcast May 14, 1967, [R35A] (Box 17)
        - Program #18: "The Yankee Rebel" pt. 2 / Clarence Cook Little; Samuel Dana; William Paton; Margaret Tracy; Alexander Grant Ruthven, broadcast May 21, 1967, [R36A] (Box 17)
        - Program #19: "Ruthven, Rackham, and Radicals" pt. 1 / Alexander Grant Ruthven; Clarence Cook Little; George Carrothers; I. Leo Sharfman; E. Blythe Stason, broadcast May 28, 1967, [R37A] (Box 18)
        - Program #20: "Ruthven, Rackham, and Radicals" pt. 2 / Alexander Grant Ruthven; Arthur Dunham; Ralph Sawyer; Charles Sink; George Carrothers; Preston Slosson; A.D. Moore; Margaret Tracy; Howard Peckham; Henry Frieze Vaughn, broadcast June 4, 1967, [R38A] (Box 18)
        - Program #21: "Michigan at 125 Years" / Margaret Tracy; Alexander Grant Ruthven; A.D. Moore; William Paton; Preston Slosson; Ralph Sawyer, broadcast June 11, 1967, [R39A] (Box 18)
        - Program #22: "The Age of the Atom" / Ralph Sawyer; Roscoe Bonnisteel; Charles Kennedy; Alexander Grant Ruthven; Harlan H. Hatcher, broadcast June 18, 1967, [R40A] (Box 18)
      - "Treasures Off the Shelf", 1 reel of 13 retained
        (award-winning dramatization based on materials in the William L. Clements Library])
        - Program #8: "The Long Siege" [Fort Detroit in the Pontiac War], broadcast November 23, 1949 (Based on the diary of Jehu Hay), 3 3/4 ips; [R41A] (Box 18)
      - [Tribute to] Waldo Abbot [documentary] / E.G. Burrows, et al. November 18, 1964, [R42A] (Box 18)